Vampire Lust for the Master Race!
Pure Blood is a horror, thriller film directed by Ken Kaplan.
Combining a new age black maid, blood-drinking zombie racists and a plot to poison the town with blood cakes, what ensues
is a dark comedy that pits the forces of fascism against the redeeming power of true love and home cooking…
Faan, played by Carl Beukes.
Gertrude, played by Aletta Bezuidenhout.
Young Gertrude, played by Amanda Lane.
Dr. Martin, played by Joss Levine.
Becky, played by Emily McArthur.
Hope, played by Nomsa Nene.
Blood: The Last Vampire (stylized in all caps) is a 2000 Japanese animated action horror film directed by Hiroyuki Kitakubo and written
by Kenji Kamiyama; the film is created by Production I.G, who also produced the film alongside their IG Plus division.
Distributed by Sony Pictures Entertainment, a girl named Saya (Youki Kudoh), who hunts the hematophagous-bat-like
creatures called Chiropterans, is tasked to eliminate the creatures at Yokota Air Base by her handlers.
Blood: The Last Vampire first premiered at Fantasia International Film
Festival on July 27, 2000, and later in Japan on November 18.
Manga Entertainment licensed the film and released it theatrically in the United
States in Summer 2001, and later on August 3 through home media release.
Blood: The Last Vampire spawned a sequel manga, three light
novels and a video game from 2001 to 2006.
It also spawned two anime series: Blood+, which aired
from 2005 to 2006, and Blood-C in 2011.
A live-action film adaptation with the same title was released in 2009.
The film explores themes of vampire, sexploitation, slasher,
nazisploitation (nazi exploitation film).
The tone is dark and intense.